

# **AAYANJIT BHUYAN**

## ReactJs Developer

I am a frontend web-dev professional with 1 year of work experience with ReactJs, I specialize in building, deploying and maintaining SPAs using ReactJs and other technologies. I believe in a mobilefirst approach and focus on building responsive web applications with refined user experience.

#### CONTACT

+6000357883 aayan.work99@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaya njit-bhuyan-b48705195

#### SKILL

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- ReactJs
- Redux
- TailwindCSS
- Bootstrap
- · Git, Git-Hub

### **EDUCATION**

Kalinga Instute of Industrial Technology **Electronics and Electrical Engineering** 2017 - 2021

#### **EXPERIENCE**

> ReactJs Developer CodeGama. 08.2021 - present

>Jr Frontend Developer Clemenzie Communications. 12.2021-08.2022

### **PROJECTS**

- Netflix Clone ReactJs and Firebase application.
- Crptocurrency tracker application - React application for exploring basic react concepts like state, props, hooks and API integration.

### **INTREST**







